internetpolyglot.com 2019-12-16

# Privacy Policy

Your privacy is our top concern. We work hard to earn and keep your trust, so we adhere to the following principles to protect your privacy: 

  * We will never rent or sell your personal information to third parties for marketing purposes 
  * We will never share your contact information with another user, unless both of you choose to contact one another 
  * Any sensitive information that you provide will be secured with all industry standard protocols and technology 

By using our service, you consent and agree to the information collection and use practices described in our Privacy Policy. We may periodically make changes to our Privacy Policy. It is your responsibility to review the most recent version of our Privacy Policy frequently and remain informed about any changes to it. 

## Information Collection

### Registration

In order to become an Internet Polyglot user, you can create an account on this web site. If you opt not to create an account on this web site you will be able to access only publicly shared lessons. To create an account you are required to provide username, email address, and choose a password. 

### Profile Information

Once a user, you may provide additional information in the My Account section describing your preferences. Providing additional information beyond what is required at registration is entirely optional, but enables you to better use the Internet Polyglot system. Your Profile information can only be viewed by you and the administrators of the system. 

### Information about your Lessons

Internet Polyglot is used to create language lessons. We store this data in our database. We use this information in aggregate to generate statistics and other usage information. We can opt to share this aggregate information with you, other end users, and other third parties. No detailed information about your lessons is to be shared with others unless you opt to explicitly share it to public or to other end users. 

### Cookies & Log Files

Like most web sites, Internet Polyglot uses cookies and web log files to track site usage and to improve our website and make it easier to use. A cookie is a tiny data file which resides on your computer which allows Internet Polyglot to recognize you as a user when you return to our site using the same computer and web browser. Unfortunately, if your browser settings do not allow cookies, you will not be able to use certain services of our website. Like the information you enter at registration or in your Profile, cookie and log file data is used to customize your experience on the web site. 

One type of cookie, known as a "persistent" cookie, is set once youíve logged in to your Internet Polyglot account. The next time you visit the Internet Polyglot web site, the persistent cookie will allow us to recognize you as an existing user so you will not need to log in before using the service. In order to access or change any of your privately sensitive information (like a credit card number), however, you must log in securely again with your password even if your computer contains your persistent cookie. Additionally, if you log out of the Internet Polyglot site you will need to re-enter your password the next time you visit in order to log in to your account. Another type of cookie, called a "session" cookie, is used to identify a particular visit to the Internet Polyglot site. Session cookies expire after a short time or when you close your web browser. 

Due to the communications standards on the Internet, when you visit the Internet Polyglot web site we automatically receive the URL of the site from which you came and the site to which you are going when you leave Internet Polyglot. We also receive the Internet protocol (IP) address of your computer (or the proxy server you use to access the World Wide Web), your computer operating system and type of web browser you are using, as well as the name of your ISP. This information is used to analyze overall trends to help us improve the Internet Polyglot service, but is not linked to personally identifiable information in any way. 

### Web Beacons

We allow other companies, called ad networks, to serve advertisements to Internet Polyglot users. Ad networks include third party ad servers, ad agencies, ad technology vendors and research firms. Internet Polyglot may "target" some ads to users that currently use certain languages during the session. Internet Polyglot does NOT use personally identifiable information to target ads. 

To deliver these ads properly, Internet Polyglot may include a file, called a web beacon, from these ad networks within pages served by Internet Polyglot so the networks may provide anonymized, aggregated auditing, research and reporting for advertisers as well as to target ads to you while you visit other websites. 

Because your web browser must request these advertisements and web beacons from the ad networkís servers, these companies can view, edit or set their own cookies, just as if you had requested a web page from their site. 

These general targets may also be used by ad networks to display targeted ads on other websites as a substitute for random, irrelevant ads. You will never see additional ads as a result of being a Internet Polyglot user and Internet Polyglot never provides personally identifiable information to any advertiser nor any third party. 

### Children

Our service are intended solely for persons 13 years of age and older. If you are under the age of 13 you may not access or use our service. By using our service you represent and warrant to us that you are 13 years of age or older. 

## Information Use

Internet Polyglot is an online service dedicated to helping language learners more effectively memorize new words. The information you choose to provide on this site is used to help you improve your learning experience. In addition, Internet Polyglot collects certain types of information in order to operate and improve our service to you and other users. Internet Polyglot is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. 

### Internet Polyglot Communications

Internet Polyglot will communicate with you through email and notices posted on this website. Please be aware that you will always receive certain emails from Internet Polyglot related to the proper functioning of your account, such as email notices when another user directly shares his or her lessons with you. Internet Polyglot may send you promotional information unless you have opted out of receiving such information. 

## Information Sharing

### Sharing Information With Third Parties

Internet Polyglot takes the privacy of our users very seriously. We will never sell, rent, or otherwise provide your personally identifiable information to any third parties for marketing purposes. We will only share your information with third parties to carry out your instructions and to provide specific services. For instance, we may use a credit card processing company to bill users for subscription fees. We may also retain the service of outside contractors to perform services on our behalf (for example, to help provide technical support services or deliver new products or services). These third parties do not retain, share, or store any personally identifiable information except to provide these services and are bound by strict confidentiality agreements which limit their use of such information. 

### Partnering with Other Organizations to Offer Combined Services

Internet Polyglot may partner with other online services to give you the combined results of both services. Whenever we offer such combined services, it will be clear who the partner is and it will be your choice to make use of the combined services or not. In these cases, none of your personally identifiable information will be passed from Internet Polyglot to the partner. 

## Links to Third Party Web Sites

Our service may contain links to other websites and software. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these websites or software. Please visit the privacy policies of these third party sites in order o understand their privacy and information collection practices. 

## Disclosures Required by Law

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information when we believe in good faith that an applicable law, regulation, or legal process requires it, or when we believe disclosure is necessary to protect or enforce our rights or the rights of other users. 

## No Error-Free Performance

We do not guarantee error-free performance under this Privacy Policy. We may not always catch an unintended privacy issue, despite our efforts to do so. Accordingly, we welcome your feedback regarding any privacy concerns that you may have, including how we can improve our service generally. We will use reasonable efforts to comply with this Privacy Policy and will take prompt corrective action when we learn of any failure to comply with it. We will not be liable for any damages, including incidental, consequential, or punitive damages, relating to the practices described in this Privacy Policy.
